teacollection.com 2018-09-07

# Privacy Policy | Tea Collection

Tea Collection respects your right to privacy. We may change or add to this privacy policy at any time without notice, so we encourage you to review it periodically. Tea Collection reserves the right to vary this policy from state to state as required by law. By purchasing our products or using our website, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with the following privacy policy.

This privacy policy will tell you:

  * What information is collected by Tea Collection
  * How we may use and share information
  * How we protect the information
  * How you may contact Tea Collection

## WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

### Consumer Information

We receive and may keep information voluntarily given to us when you decided to make a purchase from Tea Collection, register on the TeaCollection.com website, sign up for our Stay In Touch emails, or any other time you provide any information about yourself.

This information may include:

  * Your name, address and phone number
  * Date of birth
  * Your e-mail address
  * Your credit card number
  * Name and ages of children
  * Any other information you voluntarily provide

It might also include information you provide us about other people. For example, you may provide us with some of the same information as above (name and address) for a merchandise gift recipient. When you provide us with personal information about the intended recipient of a shipment, we use that information for the purposes of processing the shipment and, in some cases, to communicate with the intended recipient to provide information pertaining to the status of the shipment. We rely on you to obtain the intended recipient's consent to our use of their personal information for these limited purposes.

### Information from Other Sources

We may receive information about you from other sources such as updated address information. This information may help us to improve our ability to serve your needs such as ensuring the accurate delivery of direct mail materials.

### Use of Cookies and Other Technology

We want you to be aware that certain online tools exist to help us serve and recognize you when you visit one of our websites. For your convenience, to help us personalize your experience or better serve your needs, we may receive and store certain types of information when you visit our website. You may be familiar with the term "cookies." These cookies may be placed on your computer when you visit our site. Cookies do not provide any personal information but they allow us to understand how users navigate to and around our website, view product pages, access content and make purchases.

## ONCE INFORMATION IS RECEIVED, HOW IS IT USED AND/OR SHARED?

### Within Tea Collection

Information we collect from you may be shared between all points of contact within Tea Collection and our distribution center. We use this information to provide Stay in Touch emails relevant to you and to ship you your orders.

In addition, we may use such information to:

  * Provide you with timely and reliable fulfillment of requests
  * Do all things necessary to administer those services
  * Deliver merchandise and services that you purchase online
  * Register you on TeaCollection.com
  * Facilitate payment for your purchases
  * Confirm your orders and delivery information
  * Respond to your customer service inquiries or requests
  * Communicate offers, benefits and featured items to you
  * Administer giveaways, contests, birthday programs and similar promotions
  * Find and stock the products you want
  * Customize your shopping experience

### Outside Tea Collection

The information that you give us and information about your order may be combined with other personally identifiable information (such as demographic information and past purchase history) available from our records and other sources. This information will be used to make our future marketing efforts more efficient. This information may also be shared with other marketers to bring you offers of interest. If you prefer that we do not share your name and address with other marketers, please email us at [service@teacollection.com](mailto:service@teacollection.com). We use a third party service to collect, process and/or store information regarding consumer preferences related to our products and our websites. This third-party service provider may use cookies and transparent GIF files to collect information on the our websites as a part of the service. You may review this third-party service provider's privacy policy at www.Alvakids.com/privacy.html.

We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when (1) permitted or required by law, or (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions, or (3) investigating fraud that has already taken place. In addition, Tea Collection reserves the right to disclose personal information to a third party if a law, regulation, search warrant, subpoena or court order legally requires or authorizes us to do so.

### Retention of Personal Information

Tea Collection retains your personal information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purpose(s) for which it was collected and to comply with applicable laws. Your consent to such purposes(s) remains valid after any termination of our relationship with you.

### Right to Transfer

Tea Collection also reserves the right to disclose and/or transfer personal information to a third party in the event of a proposed or actual purchase, sale (including, but not limited to, liquidation, realization, foreclosure or repossession), lease, merger, amalgamation or any other type of acquisition, disposal, transfer, conveyance or financing of all or any portion of Tea Collection or of any of the business assets or a division thereof. Tea Collection may decide to retain a copy of the information after the sale or transfer for any use.

### HOW TO REMOVE YOUR NAME FROM OUR EMAILING LIST

When you fill out one of our forms or other requests for information, you may choose to receive email that informs you about new merchandise in our stores or online, as well as special offers and promotions. In addition, we may send you emails to help us learn more about you and your preferences. If, after you have shared your email address with us, you decide that you do not want to receive e-mail from us, you have several options to let us know of your preferences:

  * You can stop future emails by clicking on the link shown in the footer of every TeaCollection email and unsubscribe from our list.
  * Call us at 866.374.8747 and ask to have your name removed from our emailing list.

As it relates to questions you might have about our Privacy Policy or if you have a concern that Tea Collection may have failed to adhere to this Privacy Policy, please call customer relations at 866.374.8747, e-mail [service@teacollection.com](mailto:service@teacollection.com), or write us as follows:

Tea Collection  
c/o Director of Customer Service  
1 Arkansas St. Studio B  
San Francisco, CA 94107  

You may also contact us in any one of the above ways to request access to or correction or update of your personal information.

### HOW TO REMOVE YOUR NAME FROM OUR CATALOG LIST

When you fill out one of our forms or other requests for information, you may start receiving catalogs from us. If you no longer wish to receive a catalog, please email us at [service@teacollection.com](mailto:service@teacollection.com).

## MISCELLANEOUS

### Our Policy on gathering information from and communicating with children online

We recognize the unique privacy concerns regarding children. Pursuant to COPPA guidelines, we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information online from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian is made aware that a child under the age of 13 has provided us with personally identifiable information without their consent, please contact us at 877.374.8747, by e-mail at [service@teacollection.com](mailto:service@teacollection.com), or at the address listed above, and we will remove the information about the individual from our database.

### Our Commitment to Data Security

Tea Collection makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure that personal information collected from you is protected against loss and unauthorized access. This protection applies in relation to information stored in both electronic and hard copy form. Tea Collection uses industry standard security techniques on our websites to help protect against the loss, misuse or modification of information that you have provided. When you access your personal information or transmit personally identifiable data to us, that information is stored on servers that we have used commercially reasonable efforts to protect from unauthorized access or intrusion. While we implement the above security measures, you should be aware that 100% security is not possible.

### What happens if I hit a link to another site from TeaCollection.com?

Our website provides links to other websites. Other sites have their own terms of use and privacy and security policies. Tea Collection is not responsible for how such third parties collect, use or disclose your personal information. If you choose to visit one of these sites, you may want to review the policies that govern that particular site.

### Your California Privacy Rights

Beginning January 1, 2005, under California's "Shine the Light" law, California residents who provide personal information in obtaining products or services for personal, family or household use are entitled to request and obtain from us once a calendar year information about the customer information we shared, if any, with other businesses for their own direct marketing uses. If applicable, this information would include the categories of customer information and the names and addresses of those businesses with which we shared customer information for the immediately prior calendar year (e.g., requests made in 2005 will receive information regarding 2004 sharing activities).

To obtain this information, please send an e-mail message to [service@teacollection.com](mailto:service@teacollection.com) with "Request for California Privacy Information" on the subject line and in the body of your message. We will provide the requested information to you at your e-mail address in response. Please be aware that not all information sharing is covered by the "Shine the Light" requirements and only information on covered sharing will be included in our response.
